

Profile

I am a Web Developer with focus on frontend development. I have experience as a React Developer with Javascript and TypeScript. I am good at developing the features with a good connection of business value and user experience. User experience and interfaces is the most important for me! I have worked in a start-up environment and large corporate teams. I contributed in international environment and I understand the importance of good communication.

Employment History

Full Stack Developer (FERN, MERN), Freelance, Paris Area, France

JANUARY 2021 - PRESENT

Web developer specialized in building exceptional digital experiences. I help with developing solutions with FERN and MERN stack.

Technical Partner & Co-Founder, Soleilex, Paris Area, France

FEBRUARY 2021 - PRESENT

- Designed and developed the company website and a custom CRM with React.js to gather leads and manage clients in an efficient way.
- Launched targeted ads through Google Ads, Facebook for lead generation.

Product Owner, Project Manager, Societe Generale, Paris Area, France

SEPTEMBER 2019 - NOVEMBER 2020

- Delivered an internal web application for 200 international users as a Product Owner in Agile Software Development after leading the UX/UI Design, Prototyping and User Research with 10 countries, saving 250-300K€.
- Managed over 30 workshops with Customer Centricity and Collective Intelligence tools to deliver more user-friendly solutions.
- Supported SG Insurance entities in Germany, Italy, Poland, Czech Republic, Romania, Morocco, Luxembourg, Russia for various projects.

Marketing Assistant, London Stock Exchange Group, Paris Area, France

MARCH 2019 - AUGUST 2019

- Managed the relations with the developers for UX and SEO improvements.
- Designed and distributed email newsletters through Sendgrid and Mailchimp.
- Created analytical reports after processing the data from web analytic tools.

Journalist, Yeni Asya (Daily National Newspaper), Istanbul, Turkey

SEPTEMBER 2015 - JULY 2017

Education

Master's Degree in International Business Management MIB, Université Paris Dauphine, Paris

SEPTEMBER 2019 - NOVEMBER 2020

Master's Degree in International Business Administration MBA, IAE Gustave Eiffel, Paris

SEPTEMBER 2018 - AUGUST 2019

Bachelor's Degree in Business Administration BBA in Math & Statistics, Faculty of Management, Marmara University, İstanbul

SEPTEMBER 2014 - JUNE 2018

Projects

Soleilex Company Website and Custom CRM, Find My Allergy App, SG Intranet. Projects are available on my personal website mustafa-onal.com

Details

Paris France +33 7 67 23 24 48 mustafasaitonal@outlook.com

Links

Website: mustafa-onal.com
LinkedIn: /mustafasaitonal
GitHub: /neddl
Stackoverflow

Languages

English

French

Turkish

Skills

IT Project Management Multicultural Communication Complex Problem Solving Analytical Thinking Skills

Scrum, Agile Software Development

HTML, CSS
JavaScript, TypeScript
React.Js, Next.Js
Node.Js, Express.Js

Redux.js/Toolkit (Certified)
Material UI, Styled-components
Tailwind CSS, Storybook
Formik, Yup, Quill, Maps API

Axios, RESTful API Firestore, Firebase Auth MongoDB, Mongoose

Adobe XD, Sketch, Figma
VS Code, ESLint, Prettier
Git, GitHub, GitLab
UX/UI Design, User Research